<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Xenocid's Lair]]></title>
  <link href="http://xenocid.com/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://xenocid.com/"/>
  <updated>2012-08-29T14:26:57-07:00</updated>
  <id>http://xenocid.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Alex Koloskov]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Morning Coffee #2]]></title>
    <link href="http://xenocid.com/blog/2012/08/29/morning-coffee-number-2/"/>
    <updated>2012-08-29T14:20:00-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://xenocid.com/blog/2012/08/29/morning-coffee-number-2</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<ul>
<li><a href="http://thosewhomake.com/">Collection of very cool videos about people who make stuff with their hands</a>.</li>
<li>I&#8217;m not backing up KickStarter projects very often (few are quite interesting, but too pricey), but in this case it was a slam dunk. <a href="http://www.kickstarter.com/projects/kaffeologie/s-filter-a-reusable-coffee-filter-for-aeropress">Kaffeologie launched a metal S-filter for the AeroPress</a>. <img src="http://s3.amazonaws.com/ksr/assets/000/069/956/23d15ab52ab8034c29ea140aea25f2b8_large.jpg?1342331589" alt="" /> And AeroPress happens to be my favorite way of brewing coffee while I&#8217;m in the office away from other coffee-brewing toys. <a href="www.marco.org">Marco Arment</a> (who is a much bigger coffee snob than I am) also wrote a <a href="http://www.marco.org/2012/08/04/kaffeologie-s-filter">very positive review</a>. And last, but not least those guys are local (to Seatlle) and these days the word &#8220;local&#8221; immediately adds +2 to Charisma to almost anything (at least in my book). They promise to ship it in September, so I guess I&#8217;ll try it pretty soon.</li>
<li>My friend Erik wrote <a href="http://thebucketlistsociety.com/2012/08/05/how-to-actuallyclimb-a-mountain-actually/">a long and interesting article</a> about his preparations to summit <a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Mount_Rainier">Mt. Rainier</a>. This is definitely on my bucket list too and I really admire Erik&#8217;s determination in executing this dream.</li>
</ul>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Morning Coffee #1]]></title>
    <link href="http://xenocid.com/blog/2012/07/08/morning-coffee-number-1/"/>
    <updated>2012-07-08T23:32:00-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://xenocid.com/blog/2012/07/08/morning-coffee-number-1</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<ul>
<li><a href="http://www.macsparky.com/">David Sparks</a> did a <a href="http://www.macsparky.com/blog/2012/7/3/function-key-management-with-palua-screencast.html">short screencast</a> on the little app called <a href="http://click.linksynergy.com/fs-bin/stat?id=Vg6WGCcESLE&amp;offerid=146261&amp;type=3&amp;subid=0&amp;tmpid=1826&amp;RD_PARM1=http%253A%252F%252Fitunes.apple.com%252Fus%252Fapp%252Fpalua%252Fid431494195%253Fmt%253D12%2526uo%253D4%2526partnerId%253D30">Palua</a>, which allows you to switch your functional keys between, well…, being functional keys or being keys with Apple-specific functions (like brightness or volume control etc.) In other words, if you&#8217;re using function keys a lot and you&#8217;re struggling with pressing Fn + function key (which on my Macbook Pro are respectively top and bottom rows of the keyboard), then you would love <a href="http://click.linksynergy.com/fs-bin/stat?id=Vg6WGCcESLE&amp;offerid=146261&amp;type=3&amp;subid=0&amp;tmpid=1826&amp;RD_PARM1=http%253A%252F%252Fitunes.apple.com%252Fus%252Fapp%252Fpalua%252Fid431494195%253Fmt%253D12%2526uo%253D4%2526partnerId%253D30">Palua</a> . Personally, I think the best feature of the app is an ability to set the default mode for each individual app, so let&#8217;s say I want to use function keys in Vim and don&#8217;t want to press Fn each and every time, then I can make function keys mode to be default for Vim. Oh, and the best part - it&#8217;s just a buck.</li>
</ul>


<iframe width="" height="" src="http://player.vimeo.com/video/45114251 " frameborder="0" webkitAllowFullScreen mozallowfullscreen allowFullScreen></iframe>


<ul>
<li>Really glad to see that <a href="http://www.kickstarter.com/projects/260688528/clang">Neal Stephenson&#8217;s Clang project on Kickstarter</a> actually reached its goal of 500k, which means that it may actually happen now. I&#8217;m interested in the concept and though the fact that it&#8217;s going to be a PC game makes it less interesting for me (my gaming is now pretty much exclusively on iPad and Xbox (well, and on a Mac too)), still it&#8217;s an interesting project and I wish it well. Plus they&#8217;re here, in Seattle, which makes it infinitely cool.</li>
</ul>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Test_post]]></title>
    <link href="http://xenocid.com/blog/2012/04/27/test_post/"/>
    <updated>2012-04-27T00:00:00-07:00</updated>
    <id>http://xenocid.com/blog/2012/04/27/test_post</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Liquid error: undefined method `map&#8217; for &#8220;\n&#34;Love, be loved and never stop learning&#8230;&#34;\n&#8221;:String</p>

<p>It will take some experimentation to get up to speed with the Octopress, but I like it so far</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
